vebidoo.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy | vebidoo | people search blog

## General statement

This Privacy Policy applies to www.vebidoo.com (“Website”), which is owned and maintained by Vebidoo GmbH (“Vebidoo”). The Website is a people search engine that provides personal information about people (including images, videos, contacts, social networks) when entering a first name/last name combination. All information you can access when performing a people search on the Website is gathered from generally available, publicly accessible sources on the Internet. 

This Privacy Policy describes in which ways we can access and use your personal information, if any, when you use our website. Or in other terms: You can find herein information on the purpose, nature, and scope of the collection, processing, and use, if any, of your personal information disclosed by you by accessing the Website.

## Links

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Vebidoo on the Website. Other websites, which you may access via links on the Website, may have different privacy practices, thus it is advised to read their applicable privacy policy.

By using the Website and our services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. Vebidoo reserves the right to change these Terms and Conditions at any time, and by using the Website or the respective services following such modification you will assent to and accept the revised terms.

## Processing of data while using the Vebidoo website

You may use Vebidoo without having a user account. We therefore do not ask you for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number or any other information that may be used to identify you. However, when you use our website, you submit to us certain information, which includes: your browser type, your operation system, your display resolution, if you are logged into Facebook, Twitter or Google accounts, and your IP address. We do not store any of these data, but you can view them when clicking on our [internetcheck feature](http://www.vebidoo.com/internetcheck "featrure vebidoo internetcheck"). We collect, however, statistical data on search requests submitted by our users. We use this data in order to provide you with relevant search suggestions. None of these data contains any information that may link the search request to the person submitting it.

## Data from generally available sources

Vebidoo offers a first name/last name combination search option, where general available information is shown compressed.  All information is derived from general available sources, where authors are aware of the public access of the data or might even intend publication.  
Vebidoo collects, processes, and uses only the search result presented on general available sources.

## Caching

To ensure the service for a large number of users temporary first name/last name combination storages exists. The cache is updated regularly.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are sent to and (temporarily) stored on your computer when you first visit a website. Vebidoo does not enable cookies when you visit the Website. However, our partners may from time to time use cookies for better targeting their services and advertising. We do not have access to any information gathered through these cookies and are not responsible for their use. You can avoid the use of cookies by applying the appropriate browser settings. For more information on the Google Analytics Cookie, please see the next paragraph.

## Children’s Privacy

As explained above, we do not collect personal information from our users. This obviously includes users that might be under the age of 13. 

In addition, we clarify that the Website is directed to users who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, do not use the Website.

## Google Analytics

Vebidoo uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies” that are stored on your computer to allow an analysis of the use of the website. 

For more information, see <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>

## Changes of Privacy Policy and Availability

Changes in law or shift in supply by Vebidoo may require modification or addition of data to the Privacy Policy. Vebidoo reserves the right to make the necessary updates to this Privacy Policy. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy can be viewed, saved, or printed on the homepage (see Vebidoo Privacy Policy).

## Security

Vebidoo cannot guarantee the protection of data against interception, illegal usage, misuse, disclosure, or access by unauthorized third parties. Vebidoo has no possibility to control the security of other Internet sites that you might visit.

The effective date of this privacy statement is November 12th, 2012.
